<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>IPAWSCAP RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/alerts/ipaws.html</link><description>Integrated Public Alert Warning System Common Alert Protocol RSS feed.</description><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Flood Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The Flood Warning has been cancelled and is no longer in effect.</description></item><item><title>Frost Advisory</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>* WHAT...Temperatures as low as 33 will result in frost
formation.

* WHERE...Converse County Lower Elevations, Niobrara County,
East Platte County, Goshen County, Central Laramie County and
East Laramie County.

* WHEN...From 1 AM to 8 AM MDT Friday.

* IMPACTS...Frost could kill sensitive outdoor vegetation if
left uncovered.
</description></item><item><title>Flash Flood Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Corpus Christi has issued a

* Flash Flood Warning for...
Central Nueces County in south central Texas...
South Central San Patricio County in south central Texas...

* Until 630 PM CDT.

* At 326 PM CDT, Doppler radar indicated thunderstorms producing
heavy rain across the warned area. Between 1 and 3 inches of rain
have fallen. The expected rainfall rate is 2 to 4 inches in 1
hour. Additional rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches are possible in
the warned area. Flash flooding is ongoing or expected to begin
shortly.

HAZARD...Flash flooding caused by thunderstorms.

SOURCE...Radar.

IMPACT...Flash flooding of small creeks and streams, urban
areas, highways, streets and underpasses as well as
other poor drainage and low-lying areas.

* Some locations that will experience flash flooding include...
Corpus Christi, Corpus Christi International Airport, Clarkwood,
Annaville, Tuloso, and Interstate 37.
</description></item><item><title>Flood Advisory</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in San Juan has issued a

* Urban and Small Stream Flood Advisory for...
Lares in Puerto Rico...
Maricao in Puerto Rico...
Yauco in Puerto Rico...

* Until 630 PM AST.

* At 427 PM AST, Doppler radar indicated heavy rain due to
thunderstorms. This will cause urban and small stream flooding.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 327 PM CDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm over
Abilene, moving northeast at 15 mph.

HAZARD...Winds in excess of 40 mph and half inch hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
Abilene, Wylie, Hawley, Nugent, Hamby, Dyess Afb, Impact, Lake Fort
Phantom Hill, Kirby Lake and The Intersection Of Us-
180 And Farm Road 600.

This includes Interstate 20 between Mile Markers 278 and 295.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 328 PM CDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm 8
miles southeast of Castolon, or 22 miles southwest of Panther
Junction, moving northeast at 25 mph.

HAZARD...Wind gusts of 50 to 55 mph and nickel size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
Panther Junction, Big Bend National Park and Chisos Basin.
</description></item><item><title>Flash Flood Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in San Angelo has issued a

* Flash Flood Warning for...
Northwestern Callahan County in west central Texas...
Southeastern Jones County in west central Texas...
Southwestern Shackelford County in west central Texas...
Northeastern Taylor County in west central Texas...

* Until 630 PM CDT.

* At 329 PM CDT, Doppler radar indicated thunderstorms producing
heavy rain across the warned area. Flash flooding is ongoing or
expected to begin shortly.

HAZARD...Life threatening flash flooding. Thunderstorms
producing flash flooding.

SOURCE...Radar.

IMPACT...Life threatening flash flooding of creeks and streams,
urban areas, highways, streets and underpasses.

* Some locations that will experience flash flooding include...
Abilene, Hamby, Impact and Lake Fort Phantom Hill.
</description></item><item><title>Flash Flood Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in San Angelo has issued a

* Flash Flood Warning for...
Northwestern Callahan County in west central Texas...
Southeastern Jones County in west central Texas...
Southwestern Shackelford County in west central Texas...
Northeastern Taylor County in west central Texas...

* Until 630 PM CDT.

* At 329 PM CDT, Doppler radar indicated thunderstorms producing
heavy rain across the warned area. Flash flooding is ongoing or
expected to begin shortly.

HAZARD...Life threatening flash flooding. Thunderstorms
producing flash flooding.

SOURCE...Radar.

IMPACT...Life threatening flash flooding of creeks and streams,
urban areas, highways, streets and underpasses.

* Some locations that will experience flash flooding include...
Abilene, Hamby, Impact and Lake Fort Phantom Hill.
</description></item><item><title>Rip Current Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>* WHAT...Dangerous rip currents along Gulf facing beaches.

* WHERE...Matagorda Islands, Brazoria Islands, Galveston Island
and Bolivar Peninsula.

* WHEN...Until 8 PM CDT this evening.

* IMPACTS...Rip currents can sweep even the best swimmers away
from shore into deeper water.
</description></item><item><title>Severe Thunderstorm Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Midland has issued a

* Severe Thunderstorm Warning for...
West central Brewster County in southwestern Texas...

* Until 415 PM CDT.

* At 331 PM CDT, a severe thunderstorm was located 29 miles northwest
of Persimmon Gap, or 32 miles south of Alpine, moving northeast at
20 mph.

HAZARD...60 mph wind gusts and quarter size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Hail damage to vehicles is expected. Expect wind damage
to roofs, siding, and trees.

* Locations impacted include...
Elephant Mountain and Elephant Mountain Wildlife Management Area
and US HWY 118.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 331 PM CDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm over
Chico, or 9 miles north of Bridgeport, moving north at 10 mph.

HAZARD...Winds in excess of 40 mph and half inch hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
Alvord and Chico.
</description></item><item><title>Flash Flood Watch</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The Flash Flood Watch has been cancelled and is no longer in effect.</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 234 PM MDT, trained weather spotters reported a strong
thunderstorm near West El Paso, moving northeast at 20 mph.

HAZARD...Winds in excess of 40 mph and pea size hail.

SOURCE...Trained weather spotters.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
West El Paso, Northeast El Paso, Central El Paso, Anthony,
Canutillo, Westway, Vinton and Franklin Mountains State Park.

This includes Interstate 10 in Texas between mile markers 1 and 15.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 337 PM CDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm 12
miles northwest of Marathon, or 15 miles east of Alpine, moving
northeast at 20 mph.

HAZARD...Wind gusts of 50 to 55 mph and nickel size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
Alpine.
</description></item><item><title>Marine Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>A low pressure system will track northward through the eastern
Gulf of Alaska on Friday, reaching the Cross Sound region by early
Saturday morning, then shifting inland. SELY Storm Force winds of
50 to 60 knots are expected over the outside waters, with gusts
to hurricane force possible late Friday afternoon through late
Friday night. A wind shift to the west-southwest will occur behind
the low. Very high seas a likely near this low over the central
and southern outside waters with wave heights in excess of 30 feet
during the same timeframe.

For the inside waters, SELY winds will increase to 35 to 50 knots
from Icy Strait to Taku Inlet southward Friday evening, with
strongest winds in Clarence Strait and near ocean entrances.
Meanwhile, Glacier Bay and Lynn Canal will see winds ease and turn
out of the north for Friday night, but as the low shifts inland
Saturday morning, winds will shift to the south through the
northern inner channels with a spike in wind speeds of 30 to 40
knots.
</description></item><item><title>Flash Flood Watch</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Grand Junction has issued a

* Flash Flood Watch for the Grizzly Creek Fire Burn Area in portions
of northwest Colorado and west central Colorado, including the
following areas, in northwest Colorado, Flat Tops. In west central
Colorado, Central Colorado River Basin and Gore and Elk
Mountains/Central Mountain Valleys.

* Until 9 PM MDT this evening.

* National Weather Service Meteorologists are forecasting possible
heavy rainfall over the Grizzly Creek Fire Burn Area that may lead
to flash flooding and debris flows.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 442 PM EDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm over
Red Hill, moving southwest at 15 mph.

HAZARD...Winds in excess of 30 mph.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects.

Locations impacted include...
Red Hill, Socastee, Horry Georgetown Technical College Conway Campus,
Coastal Carolina University, Bucksville, Bucksport, Lighthouse Care
Center Of Conway and Conway Medical Center.
</description></item><item><title>Flood Advisory</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Memphis has issued a

* Urban and Small Stream Flood Advisory for...
Western Carroll County in western Tennessee...
Southeastern Gibson County in western Tennessee...
Northwestern Henderson County in western Tennessee...
Eastern Madison County in western Tennessee...

* Until 545 PM CDT.

* At 345 PM CDT, Doppler radar indicated heavy rain due to
thunderstorms. This will cause urban and small stream flooding.
Between 1 and 1.5 inches of rain have fallen.

* Some locations that will experience flooding include...
Jackson, Milan, McKenzie, Huntingdon, Fairview, Three Way, Atwood,
Blue Goose, Bargerton, Bemis, Carroll, Medina, Trezevant,
Clarksburg, McLemoresville, Hickory Flat, Lavinia, Mount Gilead,
Cedar Grove and Whitthorne.
</description></item><item><title>Severe Thunderstorm Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in San Angelo has issued a

* Severe Thunderstorm Warning for...
Northeastern Nolan County in west central Texas...
Southeastern Fisher County in west central Texas...
Northwestern Taylor County in west central Texas...

* Until 430 PM CDT.

* At 344 PM CDT, a severe thunderstorm was located near Nolan, moving
northeast at 10 mph.

HAZARD...Ping pong ball size hail and 60 mph wind gusts.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...People and animals outdoors will be injured. Expect hail
damage to roofs, siding, windows, and vehicles. Expect
wind damage to roofs, siding, and trees.

* Locations impacted include...
Nolan, Merkel, Trent, Camp Butman, Lake Sweetwater and The
Intersection Of Highway 70 And Ranch Road 53.

This includes Interstate 20 between Mile Markers 248 and 271.
</description></item><item><title>Severe Thunderstorm Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 345 PM CDT, a severe thunderstorm was located 21 miles north of
Sanderson, moving northeast at 20 mph.

HAZARD...Ping pong ball size hail and 60 mph wind gusts.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...People and animals outdoors will be injured. Expect hail
damage to roofs, siding, windows, and vehicles. Expect wind
damage to roofs, siding, and trees.

This severe thunderstorm will remain over mainly rural areas of south
central Pecos and northwestern Terrell Counties.
</description></item><item><title>Severe Thunderstorm Warning</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Corpus Christi has issued a

* Severe Thunderstorm Warning for...
Central Nueces County in south central Texas...

* Until 430 PM CDT.

* At 347 PM CDT, a severe thunderstorm was located over Clarkwood, or
over Corpus Christi International Airport, moving southeast at 5
mph.

HAZARD...60 mph wind gusts and penny size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Expect damage to roofs, siding, and trees.

* Locations impacted include...
Corpus Christi, Corpus Christi International Airport, Del Mar
College West Campus, Downtown Corpus Christi, Clarkwood and Tuloso.

This includes the following highways...
Interstate 37 between mile markers 1 and 10.
US Highway 181 near mile marker 648.
</description></item><item><title>Flood Advisory</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>The National Weather Service in Omaha/Valley has issued a

* Small Stream Flood Advisory for...
Northwestern Thurston County in northeastern Nebraska...
Southeastern Wayne County in northeastern Nebraska...

* Until 645 PM CDT.

* At 348 PM CDT, Doppler radar indicated heavy rain due to
thunderstorms. This will cause flooding of road ditches, culverts,
and small streams. Between 2 and 4 inches of rain have fallen.

* Some locations that will experience flooding include...
Pender, Emerson and Thurston.

Additional rainfall amounts up to 1 inch are expected over the area.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 248 PM MDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm near
Allamoore, moving east at 15 mph.

HAZARD...Winds in excess of 40 mph and penny size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Gusty winds could knock down tree limbs and blow around
unsecured objects. Minor damage to outdoor objects is
possible.

Locations impacted include...
Allamoore.

This includes Interstate 10 in Texas between mile markers 128 and
134.
</description></item><item><title>Special Weather Statement</title><link>https://www.wdfaradio.com/</link><description>At 448 PM EDT, Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm over
Oatland, or 10 miles north of Georgetown, moving southwest at 20 mph.

HAZARD...Penny size hail.

SOURCE...Radar indicated.

IMPACT...Minor damage to outdoor objects is possible.

Locations impacted include...
Graves and Oatland.
</description></item></channel></rss>